Register of the Gann-Duignan Papers, 1911-2003
Hoover Institution Archives
Gann-Duignan papers
1911-2003
72101
Hoover Institution Archives
158 manuscript boxes, 14 card file boxes, 4 oversize boxes, 1 envelope (49 linear feet)
Drafts and galleys of books by L. H. Gann and Peter Duignan, and related correspondence, photographs, and research materials relating to colonialism in Africa, the history of Northern and Southern Rhodesia (Zambia and Zimbabwe), the Rhodesian administrator Godfrey Huggins, aspects of the history of other African countries, the history of Hispanics in the United States, and the post-World War II Atlantic community.
Duignan, Peter
Gann, Lewis H., 1924-
Access
Collection is open for research. Collection stored off site; a minimum of two days notice is required for use. Boxes may be requested through Stanford's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Lewis H. Gann
1924, January 26 Born Ludwig Hermann Ganz in Mainz, Germany
1938 Fled to England from Germany
1944-1947 Interpreter with the British Army Royal Fusiliers in World War II
1950 Graduated from Balliol College at Oxford University
1950-1952 Research officer at the Rhodes-Livingstone Institute, Northern Rhodesia (now Institute for Social Research at the University of Zambia)
1952-1954 Assistant lecturer, Department of Anthropology, University of Manchester, England
1954-1963 Archivist and editor, National Archives of Rhodesia and Nyasaland
1958 Author, The Birth of a Plural Society; The Development of Northern Rhodesia Under the British South Africa Company, 1894-1914
1964 Doctorate in modern history, Oxford University
1964- Research associate, later senior fellow, Hoover Institution, Stanford University
1966 Elected a fellow of the Royal Historical Society
1967-1993 Deputy curator of the African collection, Hoover Institution
1971 Author, Central Africa: The Former British States Author, Guerrillas in History
1987 Editor, The Defense of Western Europe
1990 Visiting member, Princeton Institute for Advanced Studies
1993 Author, The United States and the New Russia
1993- Curator, Western European collection, Hoover Institution Archives
1995 Awarded the Officers' Cross of the Order of Merit of the German Federal Republic
1997 Died
Peter Duignan
1926, August 6 Born, San Francisco, California
1951 B.S., University of San Francisco
1951-1960 M.A. and Ph.D., Stanford University
1955-1957 and 1959-1960 Instructor, Western Civilization, Stanford University
1959- Curator, African collection, Hoover Institution, Stanford University; (later curator of African and Middle East collections)
1960 Became a fellow at the Hoover Institution
1960-1994 Lecturer, World Affairs Council
1962 Author, Native Policy in Southern Rhodesia, 1890-1923
1964- Member, African Studies Committee, Stanford University
1965-1966 Lecturer, Lewis and Clark College
1966- Curator of Africana, Stanford Unviersity
1968 Won the Stanford University campus volleyball championship
1968- Awarded Stella and Ira Lillick Curatorship, Hoover Institution
1969-1970 Professor, National War College
1973-1974 Guggenheim fellowship
1973-1975 National Endowment for the Humanities fellowship
1977- Curator, Middle East Collection, Hoover Institution
1979 Lecturer, History Department, UC Santa Barbara
1980-1985 Coordinator, International Studies, Hoover Institution
1985- Director, Western European Studies, Stanford University Member, European Studies Council, Stanford University
1985-1994 Lecturer, Stanford Alumni Association
1986 Editor, with Robert H. Jackson, Politics and Government in Africa, 1960-1985
1986- Board of Editors, Orbis: A Journal of World Affairs, Foreign Policy Research Institute
1988 Visiting member, Princeton Institute for Advanced Studies
1989 Author, The Hoover Institution on War, Revolution and Peace: Seventy-Five Years of its History
1993-1994 Lecturer, Seabourn Cruises
1995 Elected a fellow of the Royal Historical Society in London
2000 Author, NATO: Its Past, Present, and Future
2003 Author, with Philip Martin, Making and Remaking America: Immigration into the United States, with Martin Philip
2012 Died
Bibliography of Works by Gann and Duignan
1962 White Settlers in Tropical Africa
1967 Burden of Empire: An Appraisal of Western Colonialism in Africa South of the Sahara
1969-1975 Colonialism in Africa, 1870-1960
1972 Africa and The World: An Introduction to the History of Sub-Saharan Africa From Antiquity to 1840 Africa: The Land and The People
1977 The Rulers of German Africa, 1884-1914
1978 African Proconsuls: European Governors in Africa South Africa: War, Revolution, or Peace? The Rulers of British Africa, 1870-1914 South West Africa-Namibia
1979 The Rulers of Belgian Africa, 1884-1914
1981 Africa South of the Sahara: The Challenge to Western Security Why South Africa Will Survive: A Historical Analysis The Middle East and North Africa: The Challenge to Western Security
1983 Africa Between East and West
1984 The United States and Africa: A History
1986 The Hispanics in the United States: A History
1991 Hope for South Africa?
1992 The Rebirth of the West: The Americanization of the Democratic World, 1945-1958 The United States and the New Europe, 1985-1992 Eastern Europe: The Great Transformation, 1985-1991 Germany, Key to a Continent
1994 The United States and the New Europe, 1945-1993 An Ambivalent Heritage: Euro-American Relations Communism in Sub-Saharan Africa: A Reappraisal
1995 The New Left and the Cultural Revolution of the 1960's: A Reevaluation World War II in Europe: Causes, Course, and Consequences Political Correctness: A Critique
1996 World War II and the Beginning of the Cold War The Cold War: End and Aftermath
1998 The Spanish Speakers in the United States: A History The Debate in the United States Over Immigration Contemporary Europe and the Atlantic Alliance: A Political History
Scope and Contents note
The Gann-Duignan papers document the work and collaborative writings of Lewis H. Gann and Peter Duignan, both Hoover fellows and scholars of Africa. The collection contains drafts of books by Gann and Duignan, and related correspondence, photographs, and research materials related to colonialism in Africa, the history of Northern and Southern Rhodesia (Zambia and Zimbabwe), the Rhodesian administrator Godfrey Huggins, aspects of the history of various African countries, the history of Spanish speakers in the United States, and the post-World War II Atlantic community. The papers of both scholars are present in the collection and have not been arranged into separate groups.
Gann first met Duignan in 1959, while Gann was working at the National Archives of Rhodesia and Nyasaland. Both men became fellows at the Hoover Institution in the 1960s, co-editeding the five-volume work Colonialism in Africa. Gann and Duignan collaborated at the Hoover Institution for many years, co-writing and co-editing over thirty monographs and long essays, as well as numerous shorter articles. The scholars wrote or edited works on topics such as comparative colonialism in Africa, the economics of colonialism, United States strategic interests in Africa and the Middle East, and United States involvement in Africa since the eighteenth century. In addition to authoring many works on Africa, Gann and Duignan also wrote on topics such as Spanish speakers in the United States, immigration, the Middle East, the Atlantic community, and the Americanization of Western Europe after World War II. The Speeches and writings include drafts of monographs co-authored by Gann and Duignan, typescripts of shorter articles and speeches, and material related to their writings. The alphabetical files contain supporting materials such as correspondence and reviews, while the chronological file contains the majority of the typescripts in the collection.
The collection contains supporting material for Gann and Duignan's writings and scholarly work. The Subject file includes research material for topics such as Africa and Spanish speakers in the United States. The Incremental correspondence contains letters of Gann and Duignan, documenting their discussions with other scholars.
In addition to co-authoring many works on Africa, Gann and Duignan both served as curators for the African collection at the Hoover Institution Archives. Duignan was also active in other programs at the Hoover Institution, serving as the coordinator of the International Studies Program from 1980 to 1985. Documentation of their work at the Hoover Institution can be found in the Incremental professional activities file, as well as files on teaching and Duignan's involvement in various committees.
The Incremental photographs contain slides of Soweto, an area of Johannesburg in South Africa, while the Incremental sound recordings include interviews of members of the South West Africa People's Organization (SWAPO).
Related Collections
W. H. (William Harold) Hutt Papers, Hoover Institution Archives George Loft papers, Hoover Institution Archives Keith Middlemas collection, Hoover Institution Archives
Huggins, Godfrey Martin, Viscount Malvern, 1883-1971.; Africa--History.; Africa.; Colonies in Africa.; Europe--Foreign relations--United States.; Europe.; Hispanic Americans--History.; Rhodesia and Nyasaland--Politics and government.; Rhodesia and Nyasaland.; Rhodesia--Politics and government.; Rhodesia.; United States--Foreign relations--Europe.; United States--Foreign relations.; Zambia--Politics and government.; Zambia.; Zimbabwe.
- Biographical file, 1982
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes employment records of Gann and Duignan and writings by others describing their work.
  - "The Gann-Duignan Interpretation of History: Milieu; Method; Meaning". Unpublished essay by Robert Deutsch, typescript. Later published in Historische Zeitschrift, 1982 (Box 1)
  - Employment records of L. Gann & P. Duignan (Box 79)
- Speeches and writings, 1911-1986
  Includes typescripts and galleys of writings by Gann and Duignan, including the five-volume work Colonialism in Africa, 1870-1960. Includes card files and research materials.
  - Huggins of Rhodesia - The Man and His Country. by L.H. Gann and M. Gelfand, Interviews with Lord Malvern (formerly Sir Godfrey Huggins). Interviews with Sir Roy Welensky for the above book. Unpublished documents on the Federation of Rhodesia and Nyasaland, 1964 (Box 1)
  - A History of Northern Rhodesia: Early Days to 1953. by Lewis H. Gann, original version, 1964 (Box 1-2)
    General note
    The author was granted access to official United Kingdom and Rhodesian sources, which were closed at the time, and to which no source references could be given in the author's published study. The typescript contains the full citations.
  - Colonialism in Africa, 1870-1960, by Peter Duignan and Lewis H. Gann, 1969-1975 (Box 3-18)
    - Correspondence (Box 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 4)
    - Volume I
      - General
      - Progress reports
      - Regrets
      - Front matter and maps
      - Preface
      - Introduction
      - Index
      - Chapter 1. "African Society at the Time of the Scramble," by Elizabeth Colson
      - Chapter 2. "Trade and Authority in West Africa, 1850-1880" by Colin Newbury
        - "French Exploration and Conquest in Tropical Africa, 1865 to 1898," by Henri Brunschwig
      - Chapter 3. "Reflections on Imperialism and the Scramble for Africa," by Lewis H. Gann and Peter Duignan (Box 5)
        - "West African States and the European Conquest," by John D. Hargreaves
      - Chapter 5. "French Colonization in Africa to 1920: Administration and Economic Development," by Catherine Coquery-Vidrovitch
      - Chapter 6. "West African States and the Europan Conquest," by John D. Hargreaves
      - Chapter 7. "Nigeria: The Colonial Experience, 1880-1914," by John E. Flint
      - Chapter 9. "African Reactions to the Imposition of Colonial Rule in East and Central Africa," by T.O. Ranger (Box 6)
        - "The Congo Free State and the Belgian Congo Before 1914," by Jean Stengers
      - Chapter 10. "The British Imperial Factor in South Africa, 1870 to 1910," by D.W. Kruger
      - Chapter 11. "Uneconomic Imperialism: Portugal in Africa Before 1910," by Richard J. Hammond
      - Chapter 12. "The Germans in Africa Before 1918," by Robert Cornevin
      - Chapter 13. "Imperialism and Expansion in Ethiopia, 1865 to 1900," by Harold G. Marcus
      - Chapter 14. "Missionary and Humanitarian Aspects of Imperialism, 1870-1914," by C.P. Groves
      - Chapter 15. "Colonialism: An Episode in African History," by J.F. Ajayi
    - Volume II (Box 7)
      - Introduction
      - Preface
      - "Missionary and Humanitarian Interests, 1914-1960," by C.G. Baeta
      - "Decolonization in Africa", by Crawford Young
      - "The Colonial Era: Conquest to Independence," by A. Adu Boahen
      - "The Colonial Era in Africa: Changes in the Social Structure," by Immanuel Wallerstein (Box 8)
      - "British Policy and Representative Government in West Africa, 1920 to 1951," by K.W.J. Post
      - "British Settlers North of the Zambezi, 1920 to 1960," by George Bennett
      - "Changing Patterns of a White Elite: Rhodesian and Other Settlers," by Lewis H. Gann and Peter Duignan
      - Chapter 4. "Portuguese Africa, 1930 to 1960," by James Duffy
      - Chapter 5. "Belgian Rule in the Congo and the Aspirations of the 'Evolue' Class," by Roger Anstey
      - "Finance in Black Africa and Madagascar Between 1920 and 1945," by Hubert Deschamps (Box 9)
      - Chapter 7. "French Colonial Policy in Black Africa, 1945 to 1960," by Robert L. Delavignette
      - "Military and Police Forces in Colonial Africa", by William F. Gutteridge
      - Chapter 9. "The White Chiefs of Tropical Africa," by Michael Crowder
      - Epilogue (Box 10)
    - Volume III
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1964-1969
      - Introduction
      - "Some Effects of Colonial Rule Among the Lugbara," by John Middleton
      - "Censorship in Sine-Saloum (Senegal), 1871-1914," by Martin A. Klein
      - "From Empire to Colony: Bornu in the 19th and 20th Centuries," by Ronald Cohen
      - "Tribalism, Ruralism and Urbanism in South and Central Africa," by Max Gluckman
      - "New Elites in East and West Africa," by Lucy Mair
      - "The Impact of the Colonial Period on the Definition of Land Rights," by Elizabeth Colson
      - "The Impact of Imperialism Upon Urban Development in Africa," by Aidan Southall
      - "Urbanization and the Colour Line in Africa," by Michael Banton
      - "Colour, Categories and Colonialism: The Swazi Case," by Hilda Kuper (Box 11)
      - "Missionary Stimulus and African Responses," by F.B. Welbourn
      - "The Ngoni and Western Education," by Margaret Read
      - "Politics and Modern Leadership Roles in Ugogo," by Peter Rigby
    - Volume IV (Box 12)
      - Galley proofs with corrections
      - Uncorrected duplicate
      - Contributors. Correspondence, maps, drafts, appendices, 1971-1974 (Box 13)
        - Bauer, Peter
        - Dotson, Floyd
        - Gann, Lewis
        - Gutkind, Peter
        - Hammond, Richard
        - Hogendorn, Jan
        - Katzenellenbogen, S.E.
        - Kilby, Peter
        - Lloyd, P.C.
        - Meier, Gerald
        - Newbury, Colin
        - Pedler, Frederick
        - Peemans, Jean-Philippe
        - Van Zwanenburg, Roger
        - Wilson, Charles
        - Yudelman, Montague
      - Business (Box 14)
        - Contents
        - Preliminaries
        - Outlines
        - African (Pan) - Negritude
        - General (2)
        - Correspondence relating to non-contributors
        - Flow chart
        - Readers
      - Miscellaneous (Box 15)
        - Peemans, Frederick
        - Papers
        - Style guide
        - Rejects
        - Discards
        - Introduction materials
        - African economics (Box 16)
      - Bibliographical guide - correspondence
    - Volume V (Box 17-18)
      - Oversize galley proofs with corrections
  - African Proconsuls: European Governors in Africa, edited by Lewis H. Gann and Peter Duignan, draft, 1978 (Box 19)
  - The Rulers of British Africa, 1870-1914, by Peter Duignan and Lewis H. Gann, draft, 1978 (Box 20)
  - South West Africa - Namibia, by Peter Duignan and Lewis H. Gann, pamphlet, 1978 (Box 21)
  - The Rulers of Belgian Africa, 1884-1914, by Lewis H. Gann and Peter Duignan, draft and galleys, 1979 (Box 22)
  - Africa South of the Sahara: The Challenge to Western Security by Lewis H. Gann and Peter Duignan, oversize galleys, 1981 (Box 173)
  - The Middle East and North Africa: The Challenge to Western Security by Peter Duignan and Lewis H. Gann, 1981 (Box 24-26)
    - Galleys (Box 24)
    - Galleys and typescript (Box 25-26)
  - Why South Africa Will Survive: A Historical Analysis by Lewis H. Gann and Peter Duignan, 1981 (Box 27)
  - The U.S. and Africa by Peter Duignan and Lewis H. Gann, typescript, 1984 (Box 28-30)
  - Hispanics in the United States by Peter Duignan and Lewis H. Gann, typescript, research material, and readers' comments, 1986 (Box 31-35, 75-77)
  - Research materials for writings
    Bibliographies, clippings, printed materials, notes, drafts, photographs, maps, charts used by Lewis Gann and Peter Duignan for research.
    - African bibliography card file (Box 36-37)
    - Angolan and miscellaneous bibliography card file (Box 38)
    - Portuguese bibliography card file (Box 39-42)
    - Miscellaneous bibliography card file (Box 42-43)
    - Index cards (Box 44-46)
    - Miscellaneous materials including typescript drafts, galleys, notes, correspondence, studies, clippings, and printed matter, used by Peter Duignan, Lewis Gann and Robert H. Jackson, 1911-1984 (Box 47-51)
    - Maps, drawings, and photographs used in books by Peter Duignan and Lewis Gann (Box 52-53)
      For oversize map of Africa in 1971 originally filed in box 53, see box 173
    - "War and Society = Preliterate Man", 1982 (Box 79)
- Subject file, 1884-1974
  Includes research materials on Africa and the United States.
  - Belgian Africa (Box 54)
  - British Africa (Box 55, 78)
  - Federation of Rhodesia and Nyasaland, 1953-1956 (Box 56)
  - French Africa (Box 57-60)
  - German Africa (Box 61, 74)
  - German Africa, 1884-1914 (Box 62)
  - German and Portuguese Africa (Box 63)
  - Northern Rhodesia
    - 1890-1914 (Box 64-66)
    - 1924-1953 (Box 67-68)
  - Nyasaland, 1890-1914 (Box 68)
  - Rhodesia. "Drop 'Reformist Intervention' in Rhodesia," Dean Acheson. Reprint from The Sunday Star, Washington, D.C., 22 December 1968
  - South Africa (Box 78, 79)
  - Southern Rhodesia
    - Administrative histories of key government departments
      - 1890-1914 (Box 69)
      - 1924-1953 (Box 23, 70-71)
    - Notes on visit and miscellaneous materials, 1971 (Box 72-73)
  - United States (Box 77-79)
    Includes material on Spanish speakers
- Photographs
  Includes one photograph of Lewis Gann.
  - 1 print depicting Lewis H. Gann (Envelope A)
- Oversize material
  Includes maps used in Gann and Duignan publications
  - Maps used in publications of Lewis Gann and Peter Duignan (Box 74)
  - Duignan (Box 74)
    - Africa south of the Sahara
    - North Africa and the Middle East
- Incremental correspondence, 1965-2002
  Includes letters to and from Gann and Duignan, arranged chronologically or alphabetically.
  - Correspondence of Duignan
    - 1985-1990 (Box 146)
    - 1991-2002 (Box 133)
  - Correspondence of Gann
    - Undated (Box-folder 164: 1)
    - 1958-1959 (Box-folder 164: 2)
    - 1960-1969 (Box-folder 164: 3)
    - 1986-1987 (Box-folder 164: 4)
    - 1990-1994 (Box-folder 164: 5-7)
    - 1993-1996 (Box-folder 138: 1-5)
  - Correspondence of Gann, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 81: 1-12)
  - Abenheim, Donald, 1987 (Box-folder 81: 13-14)
  - Adenauer Stiftung, Konrad, 1988 (Box-folder 81: 15-16)
  - Alum, Roland, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 81: 17)
  - Ansprenger, Franz, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 82: 1)
  - Asiwaju, Anthony, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 82: 2)
  - Ayittey, George, 1990 (Box-folder 82: 3)
  - Bark, Dennis L., undated (Box-folder 82: 4)
  - Blackwell, Basil, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 82: 5)
  - Brown, Carl, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 82: 6)
  - Bruné, Paulin, 1985 (Box-folder 82: 7)
  - Calvert, Michael, 1974 (Box-folder 82: 8)
  - Cambridge University Press, West Project, 1987, undated (Box-folder 82: 9-10)
  - Carland, John, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 82: 11)
  - Caro, Robert A., 1990 (Box-folder 82: 12)
  - Chamberlain, Chris, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 82: 13)
  - Cohen, William, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 82: 14)
  - Cohen, Michael J., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 82: 15)
  - Collins, Robert O., 1975-1981 (Box-folder 82: 16)
  - Croom-Helm, David and Christopher, 1977-1987 (Box-folder 82: 17-18)
  - Crossey, Moore, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 82: 19)
  - Cunningham, Simon, 1981 (Box-folder 82: 20)
  - Czaplinski, Marek, 1983 (Box-folder 82: 21)
  - Damis, John, 1980 (Box-folder 82: 22)
  - Davis, Sam, 1977 (Box-folder 82: 23)
  - Demoz, Abrahaman, 1980 (Box-folder 82: 24)
  - Desfosses, Helen, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 82: 25)
  - Diamond, Larry, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 82: 26-27)
  - Diamond, Larry (Contd.), 1986-1990 (Box-folder 83: 1)
  - Djamson, E. C., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 83: 2)
  - Dumett, Raymond, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 83: 3)
  - Dyer, Colin, 1979 (Box-folder 83: 4)
  - Fadiman, Jeff, 1984 (Box-folder 83: 5)
  - Falcoff, Mark, 1981 (Box-folder 83: 6)
  - Fieldhouse, David K., 1975-1979 (Box-folder 83: 7)
  - Frankel, S. H., 1976-1979 (Box-folder 83: 8)
  - Friedrich, Wolfgang-Uwe, 1987 (Box-folder 83: 9)
  - Frost, Richard, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 83: 10)
  - Gailey, Harry, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 83: 11)
  - Greenwood Press, 1988 (Box-folder 83: 12)
  - Gregory, Christopher, 1988 (Box-folder 83: 13)
  - Gress, David R., undated (Box-folder 83: 14)
  - Gunther, Schmidt, 1982 (Box-folder 83: 15)
  - Harrison, Alexander, 1989 (Box-folder 83: 16)
  - Henriksen, Thomas, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 83: 17)
  - Holm, John D., undated (Box-folder 83: 18)
  - Hill, Robert, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 83: 19)
  - Hopkins, Elizabeth, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 83: 20)
  - Hurewitz, J. C., 1976 (Box-folder 83: 21)
  - Jones, Colin, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 83: 22)
  - Karaosmanoglu, Ali, 1980 (Box-folder 83: 23)
  - Karis, Thomas G., 1980 (Box-folder 83: 24)
  - Kimble, David, undated (Box-folder 83: 25)
  - Kirk-Greene, A. H. M., 1974-1989 (Box-folder 83: 26)
  - Knoll, Arthur, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 83: 27-28)
  - Kramer, David, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 84: 1)
  - Kubicek, Robert V., 1984-1986 (Box-folder 84: 2)
  - LeVine, Victor, 1984 (Box-folder 84: 3)
  - Lipstadt, Deborah, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 84: 4)
  - Luckett, W. T., 1987-1988 (Box-folder 84: 5)
  - Mangan, J. A., 1987-1988 (Box-folder 84: 6)
  - Maxwell, Kenneth, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 84: 7)
  - Middlemas, Keith, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 84: 8)
  - Minter, William, 1987 (Box-folder 84: 9)
  - Mitchell, Richard P., 1976-1981 (Box-folder 84: 10)
  - Munger, Edwin S., 1966-1968 (Box-folder 84: 11)
  - Murphree, Marshall, 1989 (Box-folder 84: 12)
  - Nelson, Dan, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 84: 13)
  - Norquist, N. P., 1988 (Box-folder 84: 14)
  - Oneal, John, 1990 (Box-folder 84: 15)
  - Passmore, Gloria, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 84: 16)
  - Ortega, Pat, 1989 (Box-folder 84: 17)
  - Persell, Michael S., 1972-1977 (Box-folder 84: 18)
  - Perusse, Roland I., 1983-1984 (Box-folder 84: 19)
  - Pogrund, Benjamin, 1965-1978 (Box-folder 85: 1)
  - Pheffer, Paul E., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 85: 2)
  - Roherty, James M., 1984-1990 (Box-folder 85: 3)
  - Rosberg, Carl, 1967-1978 (Box-folder 85: 4)
  - Radu, Michael, 1987 (Box-folder 85: 5)